{
    "subject": "resource/Prabhakar_Panshikar",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/India",
    "human_readable": "Prabhakar Panshikar was born in India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9326253533363342,
            "question": "Where was Prabhakar Panshikar born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7741018533706665,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from India named Prabhakar Panshikar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7559443116188049,
            "question": "What country is Prabhakar Panshikar from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7432944178581238,
            "question": "What is the significance of India in Prabhakar Panshikar's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7108376026153564,
            "question": "Can you provide any historical context related to Prabhakar Panshikar's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.666489839553833,
            "question": "What is Prabhakar Panshikar known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5454338788986206,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Prabhakar Panshikar's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5334997177124023,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Prabhakar Panshikar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3093200623989105,
            "question": "Has Prabhakar Panshikar received any awards or recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24841241538524628,
            "question": "Do you know if Prabhakar Panshikar has written any books?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Prabhakar Panshikar was born in India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8361_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Prabhakar Panshikar received any awards or recognition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8361_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Prabhakar Panshikar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8361_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Prabhakar Panshikar's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8361_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8361_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Prabhakar Panshikar was born in Bombay (which is now Mumbai, a city in India), and his early life details are rooted in Phanswadi, Mumbai. Therefore, the information supports the statement that he was born in India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the context information states that Prabhakar Panshikar was born in Mumbai, Maharashtra, India.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}